<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on The Nation of bingChilling Amnesty Coalition</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on The Nation of bingChilling Amnesty Coalition</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the Nation of bingChilling Amnesty Coalition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-us&#34;&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Nation of Bingchilling Amnesty Coalition (N.B.A.C.) is a grassroots organization dedicated to promoting freedom, curiosity, and joy in our world today. Our slogan, &amp;ldquo;#staycuriousANDkeepsmilin,&amp;rdquo; encapsulates our core beliefs and the principles we strive to embody.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Embracing Curiosity: We believe that true freedom lies in the ability to explore, question, and learn without fear or restriction. By advocating for an environment where curiosity is not only encouraged but celebrated, we aim to create a world where every individual can pursue their passions and interests with unbridled enthusiasm.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Promoting Joy: The N.B.A.C. understands that true freedom is not just about the absence of limitations but also about the presence of happiness. By advocating for an environment where joy and laughter are celebrated, we aim to create a society where people can live their lives with genuine passion and enthusiasm.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advocating Amnesty: Our dedication to advocating for amnesty is a testament to our belief in the inherent goodness and potential of every individual. By championing freedom from unjust restrictions, we work tirelessly to ensure that everyone can live their lives without fear or persecution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We believe that true freedom lies not only in the absence of limitations but also in the presence of happiness. Our slogan, &amp;ldquo;#staycuriousANDkeepsmilin,&amp;rdquo; serves as a daily reminder for everyone to stay curious about the world around them and always seek new experiences and knowledge that will enrich their lives. We are committed to creating an environment where curiosity, joy, and amnesty are not just privileges but fundamental rights for all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
